Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - N
        - Ngema, Mbongeni - Mbongeni Ngema's Sarafina!, 1988; SR-22903; Ngema, Mbongeni; Masekela, Hugh (Box 372)
          Catalog # Shanachie-43052; A-side Matrix # SH-43052-A
          Shanachie
          Canada
        - Nice & Smooth - Boogie down Bronx; BK connection, 1997; SR-22904; Nice & Smooth; Rappin' Is Fundamental (Box 372)
          Catalog # SBAB 78138; A-side Matrix # SBAB-78138-A
          Street Life Records
        - Nice & Smooth - Old to the new; Blunts, 1994; SR-22905; Nice & Smooth (Box 372)
          Catalog # OAS 6112; A-side Matrix # XSS-06112-A-1A
        - Nice & Smooth - Old to the new; Blunts, 1994; SR-22906; Nice & Smooth (Box 372)
        - Nice & Smooth - Nice & Smooth, 1989; SR-22907; Nice & Smooth (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22908. 2 copies.
          Catalog # LPRE-82013; A-side Matrix # LPRE-82013X-RE1
          Fresh Records
        - Nice & Smooth - Nice & Smooth, 1989; SR-22908; Nice & Smooth (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22907. 2 copies.
        - Nice & Smooth - Old to the new, 1994; SR-22909; Nice & Smooth (Box 372)
          Catalog # 853 239-1DJ; A-side Matrix # 853-239-1-A
          Rush Associated Labels
        - Nice & Smooth - Return of the hip hop freaks, 1994; SR-22910; Nice & Smooth (Box 372)
          Catalog # PR12 3001-1; A-side Matrix # PR12-3001-1-AS/HS
        - Nice & Smooth - Old to the new; Blunts, 1994; SR-22911; Nice & Smooth (Box 372)
        - Nice & Wild - Diamond girl, 1986; SR-22912; Nice & Wild (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22913. Different discs.Promo
          Catalog # DMD 968; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-5U274-1
          Atlantic
        - Nice & Wild - Diamond girl, 1986; SR-22913; Nice & Wild (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22912. Different discs.
          Catalog # TH-106; A-side Matrix # 106-A
          Top Hits
          Hialeah Gardens, Florida
        - Nice, Rich - The rhythm, the feeling, 1990; SR-22914; Nice, Rich (Box 372)
          Catalog # L33-18154; A-side Matrix # MOT-9717-HF1
          Motown
        - Nice, Rich - Information to raise a nation, 1990; SR-22915; Nice, Rich (Box 372)
          Catalog # MOT-6288; A-side Matrix # MOT-9130-HF1 DMM
        - Nichols, Billy - Diamond ring, 1980; SR-22916; Nichols, Billy (Box 372)
          Catalog # WES-DJ-22126; A-side Matrix # 22126-A-70427
          West End Records
        - Nick The Record - Latino disco para tu E.P., 2003; SR-22917; Nick The Record (Box 372)
          Catalog # FSR 006; A-side Matrix # FSR 006 A
          Freestyle Records
        - Nick The Record - Latino disco para tu E.P., 2003; SR-22918; Nick The Record (Box 372)
        - Nickodemus - Mariposa, 2001; SR-22919; Nickodemus; Osiris; Carol C (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22920. 2 copies.
          Catalog # GSTP-7021; A-side Matrix # 25-GSTP-7021-1A
          Giant Step Records
        - Nickodemus - Mariposa, 2001; SR-22920; Nickodemus; Osiris; Carol C (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22919. 2 copies.
        - Nicks, Stevie - I can't wait, 1985; SR-22921; Nicks, Stevie (Box 372)
          Catalog # DMD-925; A-side Matrix # STDM-49352-49356-2
          Modern Records
        - Nicodemus - Boneman Connection | Diseases, 1980; SR-22922; Nicodemus; Michigan & Smilie; Michigan & Smiley (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22923. Different discs.
          Catalog # VPRD 72; A-side Matrix # VPRD 72A
          Jah Guidance
          Jamaica, New York
        - Nicodemus - Boneman Connection | Diseases, 1980; SR-22923; Nicodemus; Michigan & Smilie; Michigan & Smiley (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22922. Different discs.
        - Nicodemus - Wake up little Suzie, 1982; SR-22924; Nicodemus (Box 372)
          Catalog # C.P. 002; A-side Matrix # CP002A
          Claypot
        - Nicole - What about me, 1985; SR-22925; Nicole; McCloud, Nicole J (Box 372)
          Catalog # RAS 2346; A-side Matrix # XSS-175 142-1A
          Portrait
        - Nicole - Don't you want my love, 1985; SR-22926; Nicole; McCloud, Nicole J (Box 372)
          Catalog # 4R9-05331; A-side Matrix # XSS-174 879-1A
        - Night Bandit - Like a thief in the night, 1981; SR-22927; Night Bandit (Box 373)
          Catalog # CHP 1944; A-side Matrix # CHP-1944-AA
          Cherry Hill Productions Inc.
        - Night Trains - On your toes, 1990; SR-22928; Night Trains (Box 373)
          Catalog # BGPT 005; A-side Matrix # BGPT-005-A
          BGP Records
        - Night Trains - Checkmate, 1991; SR-22929; Night Trains (Box 373)
          Catalog # BGP 1033; A-side Matrix # 012 DM F-0911 A-1
          West Germany
        - Nightmares On Wax - A word of science (the 1st & final chapter), 1991; SR-22930; Nightmares On Wax (Box 373)
          Catalog # WARP LP4; A-side Matrix # WARPLP-4-A DMM
          Warp Records
          Sheffield, United Kingdom
        - Nijel - Dance so fine, 1982; SR-22931; Nijel (Box 373)
          Catalog # D-211; A-side Matrix # D 211 A-T1
          Fantasy
          Berkeley, California
        - Nikki - Feel the music, 1987; SR-22932; Nikki (Box 373)
          Catalog # PDI-9015; A-side Matrix # PDI-9015 A2 1-1
          FoReal Recordz
        - Nikki - Cry baby, 1987; SR-22933; Nikki (Box 373)
          Catalog # 885 961-1; A-side Matrix # 885-961-1-AS-ES
          Polydor
        - Nikki - Cry baby, 1987; SR-22934; Nikki (Box 373)
        - Nikki D - Hang on kid; Your man is my man, 1991; SR-22935; Nikki D (Box 373)
          Catalog # 44 73812; A-side Matrix # XSS-73812B-1A
        - Nikki D. - Freak out, 1993; SR-22936; Nikki D.; Nikki D (Box 373)
          Catalog # EAS 5192; A-side Matrix # XSS 5192A-1A
          Flavor Unit Records
        - Nikki D. - Freak out, 1993; SR-22937; Nikki D.; Nikki D (Box 373)
        - Nikolai, Markus - Passion, 2000; SR-22938; Nikolai, Markus (Box 373)
          Catalog # FRK12005LTD; A-side Matrix # FRK12005LTD A1
          Music For Freaks
        - Nilsson - Son of Schmilsson, 1972; SR-22939; Nilsson; Nilsson, Harry (Box 373)
          Catalog # LSP-4717; A-side Matrix # BPRS 8249-S B1A
          RCA Victor
        - Nima G. - The drift, 2000; SR-22940; Nima G.; Aron M.; Gorji, Nima (Box 373)
          Catalog # MEX 002; A-side Matrix # MEX-002-A
          Menimax Recordings
          Denmark
        - Nina - Lasst euch drauf ein, 2000; SR-22941; Nina; Coolmann; DJ Cullmann; Stylewarz; Mirko Machine (Box 373)
          Discogs says this was self-released
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # NINA-01 A DMM H.R.
        - Nine - Lyin' king, 1996; SR-22942; Nine (Box 373)
          Catalog # PRO-7451-0; A-side Matrix # PRO-7451-ADV-A
        - Nine - Lyin' king, 1996; SR-22943; Nine (Box 373)
          Catalog # PRO-7451-ADV; A-side Matrix # PRO-7451-ADV-A
        - Nine - Make or take; Uncivilized, 1996; SR-22944; Nine (Box 373)
          Catalog # PRO-7461-0DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7461-0-A
        - Nine - Whutcha want?, 1994; SR-22945; Nine (Box 373)
          Catalog # PRO-7426-0-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7426-A
        - Nine - Lyin' king, 1996; SR-22946; Nine (Box 373)
        - Nine - Nine livez (disc one), 1995; SR-22947; Nine (Box 373)
          In same jacket as # SR-22948. Double album. Annotated.
          Catalog # PRO-1460-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-1460-1-A
        - Nine - Nine livez (disc two), 1995; SR-22948; Nine (Box 373)
          In same jacket as # SR-22947. Double album. Annotated.
          Catalog # PRO-1460-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-1460-1-C
        - Nine - Any emcee; Tha cypha; Whutcha want? (Remix), 1995; SR-22949; Nine (Box 373)
          Catalog # PRO-7435-0DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7435-0-A
        - Nineteenth Whole - Smilin', 1972; SR-22950; Nineteenth Whole (Box 373)
          Catalog # EB 9003; A-side Matrix # EB-9003-A
          Eastbound Records
          Detroit, Michigan
        - Ninglish - Lite it right away, 1995; SR-22951; Ninglish (Box 373)
          Catalog # KR7352; A-side Matrix # KR 7352-A
          KRO Records
          Bergenfield, New Jersey
        - Nirvana - Jump time, 1984; SR-22952; Nirvana (Box 373)
          Catalog # TN-1225; A-side Matrix # TN-1225-A
        - Nirvana - Come as you are, 1991; SR-22953; Nirvana (Box 373)
          Catalog # PRO-A-4416; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-4416-A-SR1
          DGC
        - Nitro | Mr. Nitro - Do the damn thang!; Hennessey (remix), 1999; SR-22954; Nitro; Mr. Nitro; MOB Playas; Buccet Loc (Box 373)
          Catalog # 44 79263; A-side Matrix # XSS-79263-A
        - Nitro Deluxe - Journey to Cybotron, 1986; SR-22955; Nitro Deluxe (Box 373)
          Catalog # CR 208; A-side Matrix # CR-208-A
          Cutting Records
        - Nitro Deluxe - Let's get brutal, 1986; SR-22956; Nitro Deluxe (Box 373)
          Catalog # CR-210; A-side Matrix # CR-210-A
        - Nitro Deluxe - Hypno house, 1990; SR-22957; Nitro Deluxe; Silk (Box 373)
          Catalog # CR-241; A-side Matrix # CR-241-A
        - Nitro Deluxe - Journey to Cybotron, 1986; SR-22958; Nitro Deluxe (Box 373)
        - Nitro Deluxe - Journey to Cybotron, 1986; SR-22959; Nitro Deluxe (Box 373)
        - Nitty Gritty - Good morning teacher | Cellular phone, 1995; SR-22960; Nitty Gritty; Wise Intelligent; Bounty Killer (Box 373)
          Catalog # PRO-7437-0DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7437-0-A
        - Nitzer Ebb - Let your body learn; Warsaw ghetto, 1987; SR-22961; Nitzer Ebb (Box 373)
          Catalog # 0-20716; A-side Matrix # 0-20716-A SR1
          Geffen Records
        - Nitzer Ebb - Murderous, 1987; SR-22962; Nitzer Ebb (Box 373)
          Catalog # 0-20691; A-side Matrix # 0-20691-A-SH1
        - Nitzer Ebb - Control Im here edition number one (command control confront), 1989; SR-22963; Nitzer Ebb (Box 373)
          Catalog # 0-21111; A-side Matrix # 0-21111-A SH-1
        - Niyabingy - Make it hot | Don't tess, 1996; SR-22964; Niyabingy; Illmental Vision (Box 373)
          Catalog # LJR-2220; A-side Matrix # LJR-2220-A
          Double Exposure
        - NKRU - Seis nueve, 1993; SR-22965; NKRU (Box 373)
          Record Company not on the label or discogs
          Catalog # RDAB 62581-1; A-side Matrix # 07863 625811A-1S
        - NKRU - Seis nueve, 1993; SR-22966; NKRU (Box 373)
        - NJ 4 - How many girls you got, 1984; SR-22967; NJ 4 (Box 373)
          Catalog # SR-2836; A-side Matrix # SR-2826-A FW-NY
          Star Records
        - No Doubt - Hey baby (stank remix), 2002; SR-22968; No Doubt; OutKast; Killer Mike (Box 373)
          Catalog # INTR-10694-1; A-side Matrix # INTR-10694-1A
          Interscope Records
        - No Face - No brothas allowed, 1994; SR-22969; No Face (Box 373)
          Catalog # DMD 2144; A-side Matrix # STDM-72910-72911-72912-1
        - No Good - Ballin' boy, 2002; SR-22970; No Good; No Good But So Good (Box 373)
          Catalog # ARTDJ-01022-1; A-side Matrix # ART-DJ-01022-1 A RE
          Artist Direct Records
        - No Good But So Good - Get your shake on, SR-22971; No Good But So Good; Jiggie Gee (Box 373)
          Catalog # BASS-001; A-side Matrix # BASS-001-A
          Luke Records
        - No Good But So Good - Six o'clock in the morning, 1997; SR-22972; No Good But So Good (Box 373)
          Catalog # PVL53266; A-side Matrix # PVL-53266-28 5-35063
        - No Good - Lizard-Lizard, 1998; SR-22973; No Good; No Good But So Good; Jiggie Gee; Luke (Box 373)
          In same jacket as # SR-22974; SR-22975. Different discs.Promo
          Catalog # RDAB-65582-1; A-side Matrix # 07863-65582-A RE1
          Loud Records
        - No Good - Lizard-Lizard, 1998; SR-22974; No Good; No Good But So Good; Jiggie Gee (Box 373)
          In same jacket as # SR-22973; SR-22975. Double album.Promo
          Catalog # RDAB-67745-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-67745-1-A
        - No Good - Lizard-Lizard, 1998; SR-22975; No Good; No Good But So Good; Jiggie Gee (Box 373)
          In same jacket as # SR-22973; SR-22974. Double album.Promo
          Catalog # RDAB-67745-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-67745-1-C
        - No Good - Let's go, 1998; SR-22976; No Good; No Good But So Good; Jiggie Gee; Luke (Box 373)
          In same jacket as # SR-22977. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # RDAB-65611-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-65611-A
        - No Good - Let's go, 1998; SR-22977; No Good; No Good But So Good; Jiggie Gee; Luke (Box 373)
          In same jacket as # SR-22976. 2 copies.Promo
        - No Sisters - (You bring out) the animal in me, 1982; SR-22978; No Sisters (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-22979. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # AIM 12106; A-side Matrix # AIM-12106-A
          AIM Records
          Fairfield, Connecticut
        - No Sisters - (You bring out) the animal in me, 1982; SR-22979; No Sisters (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-22978. 2 copies. Annotated.
        - No Sisters - (You bring out) the animal in me, 1982; SR-22980; No Sisters (Box 374)
        - No Smoke - Koro-Koro (remix), 1989; SR-22981; No Smoke; Tekla, Jah (Box 374)
          Catalog # WAFT 11R; A-side Matrix # WAF-T-11-R-A
          Warriors Dance
        - No Sovereign - Showdown, 1987; SR-22982; No Sovereign (Box 374)
          Catalog # 0-20599; A-side Matrix # 0-20599-A-SH1 B-26099-SH1 15017
        - No Strings Attached - Put your body in motion, 1991; SR-22983; No Strings Attached; Cordless Mike; Cee-Low (Box 374)
          Catalog # MRI0005; A-side Matrix # MRI-005-RE-1-A
          Magnum Records International
        - Nocera - Summertime, summertime ('89 remix), 1989; SR-22984; Nocera (Box 374)
          Catalog # SLX-40148X; A-side Matrix # SLX-40148-X
          Sleeping Bag Records
        - Nocturnal Rage - Way out; Get your hands out my pockets, 2005; SR-22985; Nocturnal Rage (Box 374)
          Catalog # 252525-1; A-side Matrix # 252525-1A S-56765
          Noc On Wood Records
          Seattle, Washington
        - Noel - Dancing is dangerous, 1979; SR-22986; Noel (Box 374)
          Catalog # DK 4806; A-side Matrix # ST-DK-37353-3
        - Noel - Change, 1989; SR-22987; Noel (Box 374)
          Catalog # BWAY 481 DJ; A-side Matrix # BWAY-481-A-DMM
          4th & Broadway
        - Noel - Silent morning, 1987; SR-22988; Noel (Box 374)
          Catalog # PRO-439; A-side Matrix # PRO-439-A
        - Noel - Out of time, 1988; SR-22989; Noel (Box 374)
          Catalog # PRO 469; A-side Matrix # PRO 469-A-DMM SP 1-1
        - Noferini | Noferini, Stefano - Sunny, 2003; SR-22990; Noferini; Noferini, Stefano; Guy; DJ Guy; Hilary; Costa, Hilary (Box 374)
          Catalog # LB 148; A-side Matrix # LB-148-A
          Loud Bit Records
        - N.O.I.A. - The rule to survive (looking for love), 1983; SR-22991; N.O.I.A. (Box 374)
          Catalog # TFW 1006; A-side Matrix # TFW 1006 AS RE1
          25 West Records
        - Noiseshaper - Prelaunch sequence EP, 2000; SR-22992; Noiseshaper (Box 374)
          Catalog # DIFEP14; A-side Matrix # DIF-CP-14-A1
          Different Drummer
          Birmingham, England
        - Nomad - Casual sex; All points close to none; Love on the rocks, 1998; SR-22993; Nomad (Box 374)
          Catalog # WORD71; A-side Matrix # WORD-71-A
          Dark Flow Productions
        - Nomad - With you, 2000; SR-22994; Nomad (Box 374)
          Catalog # RSM003; A-side Matrix # RSM-003-A 44759 2000-15-5 1-5
          Rasam Records
        - Nomar - Zoomin' (remixes), 1994; SR-22995; Nomar (Box 374)
          Catalog # SBDJ 78005-1; A-side Matrix # 72392 78005-1 RE-1 A S-29468 RE-1
        - Nonce - Mix tapes; Keep it on, 1994; SR-22996; Nonce (Box 374)
          Catalog # 0-41865; A-side Matrix # 0-41865-B-SR1
          Wild West Records
        - Nonce - Bus stops (where the honeys is at...), 1995; SR-22997; Nonce (Box 374)
          Catalog # 0-43518; A-side Matrix # 0 43518 A SR1
        - Nonchalant - Until the day, 1996; SR-22998; Nonchalant (Box 374)
          Catalog # MCA8P 3706; A-side Matrix # MCA 12573
        - Nonchalant - 5 o'clock, 1996; SR-22999; Nonchalant (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-24501. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # MCA8P 3691; A-side Matrix # MCA-12555-FDS1
        - Nonchalant - 5 o'clock, 1996; SR-24501; Nonchalant (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-22999. 2 copies.Promo
        - Nonchalant - Until the day, 1996; SR-24502; Nonchalant (Box 374)
          Catalog # MCA12 55200; A-side Matrix # MCA 12607
        - Nonchalant - Take it there, 1998; SR-24503; Nonchalant (Box 374)
          Catalog # MCA8P 4208; A-side Matrix # MCA13214
        - Nonchalant - Take it there, 1998; SR-24504; Nonchalant (Box 374)
        - Nonnie And The Onnies - I'm in love with a rent boy, 1985; SR-24505; Nonnie And The Onnies (Box 374)
          Catalog # FMS 62264; A-side Matrix # FMS-62264-A
        - Nookie - We can make it happen (Nookie remix), 1996; SR-24506; Nookie; NCA; Craig, R. (Box 374)
          Catalog # NLB 24; A-side Matrix # NLB 24 A-1
          Labello Blanco Recordings
          Berkshire, England
        - Nooks, George - I don't care, 1990; SR-24507; Nooks, George (Box 374)
          Catalog # MDD-050; A-side Matrix # M13-050-A
          Mr. Doo
        - Nooks, George - Come to me, 1997; SR-24508; Nooks, George (Box 374)
          Catalog # 90215-1; A-side Matrix # S-34789
          Correct Records
        - Nora - I'm falling in love, 1984; SR-24509; Nora (Box 374)
          Catalog # NYM-9; A-side Matrix # NYM-9-A
          The New York Music Company
        - Noreaga - N.O.R.E. (disc one), 1998; SR-24510; Noreaga (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-24511. Double album.
          Catalog # PENV 3077-1; A-side Matrix # PR-3077-A
          Penalty Recordings
        - Noreaga - N.O.R.E. (disc two), 1998; SR-24511; Noreaga (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-24510. Double album.
          Catalog # PENV 3077-1; A-side Matrix # PR-3077-C
        - Noreaga - N.O.R.E., 1998; SR-24512; Noreaga (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-24513. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # PENVPRO 0232-0; A-side Matrix # PR-0232 A
        - Noreaga - N.O.R.E., 1998; SR-24513; Noreaga (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-24512. 2 copies.Promo
        - Noreaga - SuperThug; Banned from TV, 1998; SR-24514; Noreaga (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-24515. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # PENVPRO 0238; A-side Matrix # PR-0238A
        - Noreaga - SuperThug; Banned from TV, 1998; SR-24515; Noreaga (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-24514. 2 copies.Promo
        - Noreaga - Holiday jumpoff II (disc one), 1999; SR-24516; Noreaga (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-24517. Double album.Promo
          Catalog # TB 2059; A-side Matrix # TB-2059 A
        - Noreaga - Holiday jumpoff II (disc two), 1999; SR-24517; Noreaga (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-24516. Double album.Promo
          Catalog # TB 2059; A-side Matrix # TB-2059 C
        - N.O.R.E. - Chosen one, 2005; SR-24518; N.O.R.E. (Box 374)
          Catalog # UBO-1061-0P; A-side Matrix # UBO-1061-0P A
          N.O.R.E.
        - Noreaga - Play that s***, 1999; SR-24519; Noreaga (Box 374)
          Catalog # TB2047; A-side Matrix # TB 2047 A
        - N.O.R.E. - Get down, 2004; SR-24520; N.O.R.E. (Box 374)
          Catalog # DEFR 16181-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16181-1A
          Roc-A-Fella Records
        - N.O.R.E. - Oye mi canto, 2004; SR-24521; N.O.R.E.; Daddy Yankee; Skyy, Nina; Big Mato; Gem Star (Box 374)
          Catalog # DEFR 16169-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16169-1A RI
        - N.O.R.E. - Nothin', 2002; SR-24522; N.O.R.E.; Cam'Ron; Cassidy; Capone; Fat Joe (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-24523. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 314 582 914-1; A-side Matrix # 314-582-914-1A X
        - N.O.R.E. - Nothin', 2002; SR-24523; N.O.R.E.; Cam'Ron; Cassidy; Capone; Fat Joe (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-24522. 2 copies.
        - N.O.R.E. - Get down, 2004; SR-24524; N.O.R.E. (Box 374)
        - N.O.R.E. - Hang, hang, 2005; SR-24525; N.O.R.E.; Ashanti; Killa 3 (Box 374)
          Catalog # DEFR 16331-1; A-side Matrix # B0004942-11A
        - Noreaga - Holiday jumpoff II (disc one), 1999; SR-24526; Noreaga (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-24527. Double album.Promo
        - Noreaga - Holiday jumpoff II (disc two), 1999; SR-24527; Noreaga (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-24526. Double album.Promo
        - N.O.R.E. - Grimey; Nah mean u heard, 2001; SR-24528; N.O.R.E. (Box 374)
          Catalog # DEFR 15436-1; A-side Matrix # 314-588-794-1-A
        - Noreaga - Play that s***, 1999; SR-24529; Noreaga (Box 374)
          Catalog # TB2047; A-side Matrix # TB2047A
        - N.O.R.E. - Oye mi canto, 2004; SR-24530; N.O.R.E.; Daddy Yankee; Nina Skyy; Big Mato; Gem Star (Box 374)
        - Norfolk - Cowboy's to girls, 1980; SR-24531; Norfolk; Norfolk Orch. (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-24532. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BJI 751; A-side Matrix # BJI-751 A
          Barbara Jean International Records Ltd.
        - Norfolk - Cowboy's to girls, 1980; SR-24532; Norfolk; Norfolk Orch. (Box 374)
          In same jacket as # SR-24531. 2 copies.
        - Norma Jean - High society, 1979; SR-24533; Norma Jean (Box 374)
          Catalog # PRO-A-839; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-839 S-1A B-14502
          Bearsville
        - Norman, John B. - I can't stop, 1999; SR-24534; Norman, John B. (Box 374)
          Catalog # CMC-0003; A-side Matrix # CMC-0003-A
          Contagious Records
        - North Side Production$ - Asalamalakum; Stop the nonsense, 1989; SR-24535; North Side Production$ (Box 375)
          Catalog # NS-2; A-side Matrix # NS-2-A
          Northside Productions
          Trenton, New Jersey
        - North South Connection - Gotta keep dancin' (Pop will eat this house mix), 1988; SR-24536; North South Connection; Legacy (Box 375)
          Catalog # 12 GERE 100; A-side Matrix # GERE-100-A+B
          GRC (General Recording Company)
        - Northeast Groovers - The water, 1993; SR-24537; Northeast Groovers (Box 375)
          Catalog # F 0041; A-side Matrix # F0041-A
          Future Records & Tapes
          Landover, Maryland
        - Northeast Groovers - Jams (disc one), 1995; SR-24538; Northeast Groovers (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24539. Double album.
          Catalog # PA-1017-1; A-side Matrix # PA-1017-A DMM NY USA 11505
        - Northeast Groovers - Jams (disc two), 1995; SR-24539; Northeast Groovers (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24538. Double album.
          Catalog # PA-1017-1; A-side Matrix # PA-1017-C DMM NY USA 11505
        - Northwest Youngins - On the move, 1995; SR-24540; Northwest Youngins (Box 375)
          Catalog # SBC713-1; A-side Matrix # SBC-713-A DMM NY USA 12464
          Sound By Charlie
          Maryland, United States
        - Norwood B. - Your on the one (your on the money), 1982; SR-24541; Norwood B.; Norwood (Box 375)
          Catalog # PWR-2002; A-side Matrix # PWR-2002-A
          Philly World Records
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Notorious B.I.G. | Twista | Bone Thugs-N-Harmony - Nasty girl; Spit your game, 2005; SR-24542; Notorious B.I.G.; Twista; Bone Thugs-N-Harmony; Diddy; Jagged Edge; Nelly; Avery Storm (Box 375)
          Catalog # PR 302066; A-side Matrix # ST-BB-94143A-1/PR-302066A-1
          Bad Boy Entertainment
        - Notorious B.I.G. - Duets: the final chapter (disc one), 2005; SR-24543; Notorious B.I.G. (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24544. Double album.
          Catalog # 83885-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-83885A-1
        - Notorious B.I.G. - Duets: the final chapter (disc two), 2005; SR-24544; Notorious B.I.G. (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24543. Double album.